# Harold Seo

# **PROFILE**

Determined and dynamic Web Developer with a passion for delivering functional, responsive, and intuitive solutions. Experience developing multi-faceted projects including a chatting web app, a two-player web game, and a website for a carbon reduction company. Equipped with a skillset, that incorporates both the knowledge and practice of front end technologies.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Freelance Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Present

Los Angeles, CA

- Developed a web application, where users can chat with one another, in groups, or with a chatbot.
- Built a fully-functional website for a freight forwarding company, providing an online presence to increase exposure.
- Worked with a team of 5 to develop a website for a carbon footprint reduction company.
- Collaborated on the conceptualization and development of a web application that notifies users when they are approaching their destination when utilizing public transportation.
- Created a web application game, where two players compete in a game of tag.

# **Operations Analyst, NBCUniversal Media, LLC**Aug 2018 - Sep 2019 Los Angeles, CA

- Enforced on infringing media content across multiple social media platforms including YouTube Content Management System and Facebook Rights Manager.
- Managed YouTube Content ID queues, claiming and/or releasing thousands of videos.
- Collaborated with the engineering team to develop and improve internal operation tools.
- Performed routine audits on asset policies to ensure smooth transitions for domestic monetization and for operational efficiency.
- Actioned on thousands of User Generated Content (UGC) both domestically and internationally for monetization or enforcement.
- Worked closely with the legal team on risk management to mitigate any imminent issues when working with disputed claims.

## CONTACT

- Los Angeles, CA
- **(**213)327-6225
- ♦ haroldseo.github.io/portfolio

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### LANGUAGES

JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

#### FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

React, jQuery, Node.js, Express, Bootstrap

## DATABASES

MongoDB, PostgreSQL

#### OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

Git & GitHub, WordPress, Heroku, AJAX

# **EDUCATION**

#### GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Web Development Immersive, 2017

#### **CSU NORTHRIDGE**

Bachelor of Science (BS) Kinesiology and Exercise Science, 2010 - 2016